skuvault.com 2018-02-12

# SkuVault Warehouse Management System · Privacy Policy

### YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS

We recognize that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important to you, and therefore, have adopted this privacy policy. This privacy policy describes our privacy practices and how we treat the personal information that we collect from you when you use our products and services, including any personal information we collected from you when you created your account. The SkuVault privacy policy applies to all of the products, services, and websites offered by SkuVault or our related, affiliated and/or subsidiary companies (collectively, the “Products and Services”).

### HOW WE APPLY USAGE INFORMATION

The purpose of reviewing customer and viewer information is to create a friendlier and more efficient experience while working with SkuVault. Personal information submitted at the time of registration may be used by SkuVault for the marketing and promotion of SkuVault products that we feel may be of interest to you. You may “opt out” of these marketing activities at any time, by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located in the footer of all marketing email correspondences. We may use demographic and/or profile data to tailor your experience on our sites, show you content that we think you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. Furthermore, we shall have the right to retain records of all data pertaining to use of the website including, but not limited to, usage, activity logs, and click-throughs. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, comments made by our customers.

### TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION

We take your privacy very seriously. None of the personally identifiable information that is collected by SkuVault is rented or sold to any third parties for any purpose. SkuVault does reserve the right to rent or sell aggregate data to third parties when grouped with other user data in an aggregate form. Information may be shared with a third party that has partnered with SkuVault under a confidentiality obligation as part of providing the SkuVault service to the customer. SkuVault must comply with all applicable Local, State, Federal and International Law regarding the disclosure of user information.

### OTHER INFORMATION

By submitting personal information to us or using our site, you agree that we may collect and use such personal information in accordance with our privacy policy or as permitted by law. If you do not agree with these terms, do not provide any personal information to us. If you refuse or withdraw consent, or do not provide us with any necessary personal information, we may not be able to provide you with products or service.

### GATHERING TECHNICAL INFORMATION TO DIAGNOSE ERRORS

While SkuVault strives to avoid errors with respect to the operation of our app, sometimes errors do occur. SkuVault tracks the use of our app in order to identify and diagnose errors so that SkuVault team can take steps to remedy them and possibly avoid them altogether. As part of this process, SkuVault collects non-personally identifiable technical information relating to the devices used by users to launch and operate the app – such as the type of device used (e.g., mobile, tablet, etc.), the operating system for device (e.g., Android, iOS, etc.), the device’s brand, and the device’s manufacturer, etc. Our goal in collecting such information is to provider users of our app with better service and a quality experience.

### REMOVAL FROM OUR DATABASE

To request removal from the database, please submit a request to info@skuvault.com and we will be happy to remove your information promptly. If you request that we modify or remove all of your personal information, we will promptly do so, to the extent possible. Once your personal information has been removed you will not be able to use our products or services unless you re-register.

### COOKIES

When you use SkuVault Products and Services, we send to your computer one or more cookies (i.e. a small file containing a string of characters) that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Products and Services by storing user preferences and tracking. We may also use cookies to keep track of your session, shopping cart, and advertising delivery. We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our sites. These ads may also contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our websites, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company and we do not have access to this information. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please note, however, some features of the Products and Services may not function properly, if at all, if your cookies are disabled.

We may allow third parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our sites and/or Products and Services. We and these companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and connect to our sites and/or Products and Services. Our sites do not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows us and these companies to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

### LINKS

We may create links to other web sites. We will make reasonable efforts to link only to sites that meet similar standards for maintaining each individual’s right to privacy. However, many other sites that are not associated or authorized by us may have links leading to our sites. We cannot control these links and we are not responsible for any content appearing on these sites.

### IP ADDRESSES

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregated uses. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### MERGER OR ACQUISITION

In the event that SkuVault merges or is acquired by another company, this privacy policy may be changed. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of our successors and assigns.

### AMENDMENTS

We may amend this policy at any time. If we are going to use personally identifiable information collected through our sites in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on our site for thirty (30) days prior to such use.

### QUESTIONS, COMMENTS, CONCERNS

All questions, comments and concerns can be submitted by emailing info@skuvault.com. You will receive an answer as soon as possible.
